A Guide to the William C. Wampler Congressional Papers, 1953-1990
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
William C. Wampler Congressional Papers, 1953-1990 (Bulk, 1967-1982)
Special Collections, Virginia Tech, Blacksburg, Va.
Ms1982-003
260.42 cu. ft.; 250 boxes
William C. Wampler, Sr. was a U.S. Congressman from Virginia in the 1950s through 1980s. His papers primarily document his tenure in Congress during the 1970s and 1980s, including correspondence with constituents, committees, and government departments, legislative files, public relations and campaign materials, and photographs.
Wampler, William C., (William Creed), 1926-
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Acquisition Information
William C. Wampler Congressional Papers was donated in three accessions to Special Collections in 1982, 1984, and 1988.
Biographical Note
William Creed Wampler, Sr. (1926-2012) was a Congressman from Virginia from 1953 to 1955 and 1967 to 1983. He served in the U.S. Navy during World War II before graduating from Virginia Polytechnic Institute (VPI) in 1948 and studying law at the University of Virginia. Wampler became a journalist in Virginia and Tennessee, while also supporting the work of the Republican Party in the Ninth Congressional District. In 1953, he was elected to the U.S. House of Representatives from Virginia, losing his seat in 1955. Wampler then joined the Atomic Energy Commission and in 1957 became the vice president and manager of the Wampler Brothers Furniture Company, followed by the Wampler Carpet Company in 1961, in Bristol. In 1967, he left the company upon succesfully winning his election to the U.S. House of Representatives, serving until he lost his seat once more in 1983. Wampler also served on the boards of visitors of Emory and Henry College and of VPI.
Source: Wampler, William Creed (1926-2012), entry in Biographical Directory of the United States Congress.
Scope and Content
The William C. Wampler Congressional Papers include legislative files, committee files (House Agriculture Committee, Select Committee on Aging, etc.), constituency correspondence, U.S. and Virginia government departmental files, public relations and campaign material, and photographs.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged by box.
Index Terms
Corporate Names:
United States. Congress. House.
Subjects:
Local/Regional History and Appalachian South
Contents List
- Appalachian Regional Commission; Correspondence; Legislation; Appointment and Guest Books; Publicity materials; Departmental: Commerce Economica Development Administration thru Small Business Association, 1962-1980 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, Committees: Agriculture and Health/Nutrition, 1977-1978 (Box 2)
- Legislation: Agriculture, Mining, Land, Business, Rural Development, 1971-1978 (Box 3)
- Appalachian Regional Commission; Correspondence; Public Relations/Media; Grants, 1974-1976 (Box 4)
- Correspondence (Box 5)
- Departmental: Consumer Safety Committee thru Health, Education, and Welfare, Military, 1978-1980 (Box 5)
- Committees, Departmental: Agriculture, Military, Aging, 1979-1980 (Box 6)
- Correspondence: Requests for recommendations (Box 6)
- Correspondence: Virginia State Republican Party thru XYZ, 1969-1970 (Box 7)
- Departmental: Agriculture thru Federal Communications Commission (FCC), 1977 (Box 8)
- Correspondence: R thru Virginia Division of Mines, 1967-1968 (Box 9)
- Correspondence: Open Door, Lee County thru Virginia Employment Commission, 1972 (Box 10)
- Departmental: Agriculture thru Health, Education, and Welfare, 1972 (Box 11)
- Correspondence: Virginia Department of Motor Vehicles thru Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 12)
- Departmental: Treasury thru Vice President, 1969-1970 (Box 13)
- Civil Defense thru Crime and Criminals, 1980-1982 (Box 14)
- Public Relations, 1977-1978 (Box 15)
- Correspondence: Misc A thru Open Door, Grayson County, 1972 (Box 16)
- Correspondence: Pembroke, Town of thru Public Relations Sevices, 1969-1970 (Box 17)
- Departmental: Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) thru Post Office, 1971 (Box 18)
- Legislation: General thru Veterans Affairs, 1971 (Box 19)
- Invitations, 1978 (Box 20)
- New River Documents thru Petitions & Analysis, Blue Ridge Hydro Project, 11975-1976 (Box 21)
- Correspondence: Clerk of the House thru Employment Administration, 1969-1970 (Box 22)
- Departmental: NASA thru Vice President, 1976 (Box 23)
- Legislation: Saccharin thru Abortion, General, 1977-1978 (Box 24)
- Correspondence: Miscellaneous T thru Virginia Department of Workman's Comp, 1967 (Box 25)
- WCW Legislation, 1969-1970 (Box 26)
- Correspondence: R thru School Superintendents, 1969-1970 (Box 27)
- Legislation: Food and Agriculture (active 1981) thru Republican Substitute to HR 603, 1981 (Box 28)
- Extensions thru Virginia Statewide Data, 1981 (Box 29)
- Invitations declined, 1981 (Box 30)
- Invitations declined, 1978 (Box 31)
- Legislation: Agriculture thru Internal Security, 1974 (Box 32)
- Military/Passports, 1978 (Box 33)
- Legislation: 13000 Health and Economic Concerns thru 16010 Right to Work, 1977-1978 (Box 34)
- Departmental: Labor thru Post Office, 1969-1970 (Box 35)
- Agriculture thru Forest Service, 1982 (Box 36)
- Miscellaneous, 1976-1977 (Box 37)
- Correspondence: Agricultural Issues, 1979-1980 (Box 38)
- Projects: Bristol thru Wythe/Bland Counties, 1973-1974 (Box 39)
- Agriculture and Energy: Land Acquisition, Rare II, Estaban, SY Fuel Conference, VPI Vet School, 1977-1979 (Box 40)
- Departmental: Army thru Department of Education, 1982 (Box 41)
- Legislation, 1981-1982 (Box 42)
- Departmental: FDAA thru Interstate Commerce Commission, 1977 (Box 43)
- Correspondence: Agriculture Issues: Predator Control thru Trade, 1978-1980 (Box 44)
- Committees: Aging, Ethics and Concerns, 1975-1982 (Box 45)
- Correspondence: Virginia Department of Welfare thru Wythe County GOP, 1971 (Box 46)
- Departmental: Agriculture thru Defense, 1978 (Box 47)
- Invitations, 1977 (Box 48)
- Local Action & Appalachian Regional Committee, 1976-1979 (Box 49)
- Departmental: Interstate Commerce Commission thru White House, 1975 (Box 50)
- Correspondence: Admission to Colleges thru Memos, 1974 (Box 51)
- Letters concerning constituents: A thru Z, 1980-1982 (Box 52)
- Departmental: Federal Energy Administration thru Interior, Wildlife and Sport Fisheries, 1975 (Box 53)
- Agenda Reminders, 1980 (Box 54)
- Legislation, 1973-1977 (Box 55)
- Legislation: Agriculture thru World War I Veterans, 1975-1976 (Box 56)
- Legislation: Agriculture Committee thru Committee on Education and Labor, 1969-1970 (Box 57)
- Invitations decline thru Student Intern Program, 1967 (Box 58)
- Departmental: ICC: Trucking thru State Department, 1978-1979 (Box 59)
- Correspondence from constituents, 1980-1981 (Box 60)
- Correspondence replying to constituents, 1981-1982 (Box 61)
- Miscellaneous, 1978-1979 (Box 62)
- Invitations declined, 1979 (Box 62)
- Public Relations files, 1981-1982 (Box 63)
- Newspaper Clippings, Elections, 1967-1968 (Box 64)
- Legislation, 1970 (Box 64)
- Campaign TV/radio spots, 1970 (Box 64)
- Departmental: Agriculture, 1981 (Box 65)
- Legislation: 96th Congress, 1979-1980 (Box 66)
- Vouchers, 1977 (Box 67)
- Miscellaneous and Legislator Orientation, 1979-1981 (Box 68)
- Departmental: Health and Human Services thru Marine Corps, 1981 (Box 69)
- Legislation, 1981 (Box 70)
- Legislation: Committee on Public Works thru NFIB Ballots, 1969-1970 (Box 71)
- Invitations accepted (April-August) thru Virginia Department of Vocational Rehabilition, 1971 (Box 72)
- Accounts and Miss Munsey's files, 1967-1969 (Box 73)
- Office Procedures and Policies thru Coal, 1978-1982 (Box 74)
- Public Relations, 1978-1979 (Box 75)
- Local Projects, 1978-1982 (Box 76)
- Departmental: National Park Service thru White House, 1981 (Box 77)
- Legislation: Agriculture thru Interior, 1967-1968 (Box 78)
- Departmental: Library of Congress thru Virginia Governor's Office, 1979-1980 (Box 79)
- Committee business, 1980 (Box 80)
- Departmental: Justice Department thru State Corporation Committee, 1978-1980 (Box 81)
- Departmental: Army Reserves thru Office of Economic Opportunity, Neighborhood Youth Corps, 1968 (Box 82)
- Speeches, 1976-1982 (Box 83)
- Legislation: WWI Vets Pension thru Tax Credit for the Elderly, 1978 (Box 84)
- Military, 1976 (Box 85)
- Invitations declined thru James Madison Memorial Commission, April 1969; 1969-1970 (Box 86)
- Correspondence: Agriculture Issues; Implementation of Trade Act of 1978 thru Republican Members, 1979-1980 (Box 87)
- Legislation: A thru Y Veterans, 1975-1976 (Box 88)
- Blue Ridge Parkway, 1979-1980 (Box 89)
- Departmental: Housing and Urban Development (HUD) thru Labor, 1977-1978 (Box 90)
- Legislation: Aging thru Merchant Marines & Fishery 1975 (Box 91)
- Departmental: Agriculture thru Federal Communications Commission (FCC), 1975 (Box 92)
- Legislation: Pros & cons, 1977-1978 (Box 93)
- Departmental: Farm Credit Administration thru Housing and Urban Development (HUD), 1974 (Box 94)
- Speeches, 1981-1982 (Box 95)
- Correspondence: Energy, Electric thru Requests, Flags, 1978-1980 (Box 96)
- Departmental: Federal Employment thru Department of Health and Human Services, 1982 (Box 97)
- Correspondence: VPI&SU (Virginia Tech), General thru Lictax, 1972 (Box 98)
- Legislation: Ways and Means thru WCW Legislation, 1971 (Box 99)
- Invitations declined and Disaster Manual, 1976 (Box 100)
- Legislation: Rules Committee/Flag Bill thru General/NFIB Ballots, 1967-1968 (Box 101)
- Photographs, 1975-1979 (Box 102)
- General Correspondence, 1976 (Box 103)
- Agriculture Committee; Miscellaneous, 1978-1979 (Box 104)
- Correspondence: Regarding Coal and FMHA, 1979-1980 (Box 105)
- Departmental: Civil Service Commissions thru Health Education and Welfare, 1969-1970 (Box 106)
- Correspondence: Virginia Department of Corporations, Trailways Bus Service (Bluefield, WV) thru Virginia Republican Party, 9th District, 1969-1970 (Box 107)
- Departmental: Agriculture thru Energy, 1980 (Box 108)
- Agriculture Committee and related papers 1981-1982 (Box 109)
- General Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 110)
- Departmental: Food and Drug Administration thru Department of Labor/Mine Safety and Health Administration, 1982 (Box 111)
- Public Relations, 1967-1968 (Box 112)
- Correspondence: Miscellaneous thru Virginia Department of Health, 1972-1973 (Box 113)
- Correspondence: F thru Q, 1968 (Box 114)
- Correspondence: Miscellaneous thru Virginia Division of Mines and Quarries, 1977 (Box 115)
- Invitations: closed and declined, 1975 (Box 116)
- Correspondence: A thru Employment (summer), 1968 (Box 117)
- Correspondence: Miscellaneous A thru Z, 1976 (Box 118)
- Departmental: Virginia Department of Health thru Veterans Administration, 1980 (Box 119)
- Correspondence: S thru Z, 1979-1980 (Box 120)
- News Releases, 1979-1980 (Box 120)
- Legislative card file, 1977-1979 (Box 121)
- Committee concerns, including Virginia Tech Vet School, world food, Welfare Subcommittee, and Republican Party of Virginia, 1977-1979 (Box 121)
- Correspondence: Photographs thru Diane N. - White House Tours, 1981-1982 (Box 122)
- Correspondence: Biography thru Office Miscellaneous/Rooms, 1981-1982 (Box 123)
- 97th Legislature Subject Files: Natural Resources/Forests and Forestry thru Prisons, 1981-1982 (Box 124)
- 97th Legislature Subject Files: Agriculture/Tobacco thru Budget, 1981-1982 (Box 125)
- Correspondence: J thru Requests, 1971-1972 (Box 126)
- Departmental: Information Agency, U. S. thru White House, 1974 (Box 127)
- Correspondence: U Miscellaneous thru William C. Sampler - Personal, 1971-1972 (Box 128)
- Agriculture: Ag Credit thru Wheat Foods, 1977-1978 (Box 129)
- Correspondence: Agriculture Committee thru Committee on Committees; Miscellaneous [official and constituent correspondence], 1975-1978 (Box 130)
- Correspondence: A thru Invitations Declined - April 1971, 1971-1972 (Box 131)
- Correspondence: N thru Superintendent Office, 1974 (Box 132)
- Card files: Calendar lists, Capitol books, flag request lists, 1974-1976 (Box 133)
- Correspondence: Press Correspondance thru Radio/TV tapes, 1971 (Box 134)
- Newspaper Clippings: 68 Campaign thru '70 Wampler in the News, 1968-1970 (Box 134)
- Photographs: Campaign Stock Photos thru "Your best bet - hire a Vet", 1978 (Box 134)
- Viirginia Departmental Files: Govenor's Office thru MiscClosed "M-Q", 1978-1980 (Box 135)
- Correspondence, HR Bills, etc. for Agriculture, Invitations, Gun Control, and assorted legislation, 1972-1973 (Box 136)
- Legislation: H.J. Res. 68 Yorktown Commemoration thru H. J. Res. 602 Newspaper Carrier Day; H. Con. Res. 35 Tax on Interest and Dividends thru H. C. Res. 412 USDA Graduate School, 1981-1982 (Box 137)
- Photographs: Agriculture Commite thru White House, 1981-1982 (Box 138)
- Correspondence: A thru XYZ., 1977-1978 (Box 139)
- Personal Files: Master Address and Phone Directory, 1978 (Box 139)
- Speeches: Big Stone Gap Labor day throu Southeaster Poultry and Egg Association., 1976-1977 (Box 139)
- Correspondence: A thru L, 1974-1975 (Box 140)
- Correspondence: K thru P, 1969-1970 (Box 141)
- Correspondence: Mics "A" thru Lonesome Pine Airport., 1977 (Box 142)
- Departmental: Justice Department thru White HouseMics "A" thru Lonesome Pine Airport., 1977 (Box 142)
- Personal Files: Barbara Wampler to White House, 1975-1978 (Box 143)
- Correspondence, Constituents: Assorted files, 1980-1981 (Box 144)
- Business Conference Files: Big Stone Gap B&ADC thru Rural Development Conference, 1974-1976 (Box 145)
- Flag Requests: Appalachia Elementary School thru Redemer Lutheran Scout Group, 1982 (Box 145)
- Public Relations: Newsletter Responses thru Finished Requests, 1979-1980 (Box 146)
- Departmental: Defense thru Library of Congress, 1976 (Box 147)
- Card files: Constituents Cases, A thru S, 1978-1980 (Box 148)
- Executive Committee Battledore, 1973-1974 (Box 149)
- Legislation: Billls Before Agriculture Committee 1st Session 94th Congress Volume 1 thru Volume 2, 1975-1976 (Box 149)
- Members's Personal Voting Record 92nd Congress thru Member's Personal Voting Record 94th Congress, 1971-1976 (Box 149)
- Invitations: The Church of Latter-Day Saints thru Westmoreland Coal Company, 1979-1980 (Box 150)
- Schedules: January thru December, 1980 (Box 150)
- Departmental: EPA thru Dept. of Labor, 1980 (Box 151)
- Legislation: Agricultural Committee thru Judiciary Committee, 1972 (Box 152)
- Legislation: M.C. Floor Privileges H.R. 1438 thru National Coal Policy H.R.9906, 1973-1976 (Box 153)
- Card files: Constituents, A thru L, 1974-1977 (Box 154)
- Local Projects: Buchanan County thru Wise County, 1978-1980 (Box 155)
- Legislation: Sugar Agreement H.R. 13750 thru Nitrite Action Delay H.R. 1320, 1977-1979 (Box 156)
- Legislation: Extension of H.R. 8841 Insectiside Act thru Sugar Act H.R. 12525, 1975 (Box 157)
- Legislation: Energy Situation/General thru Weatherization, 1980-1981 (Box 158)
- Legislation: Public Works Committe thru WCW Legis., 1973 (Box 159)
- Departmental: Dept. of HEW, Charity Car and Hill-Burton Regulations thru VA Febuary 1972, 1972 (Box 160)
- 1980 Fuel Program thru EPA, 1979-1980 (Box 161)
- Departmental: Volunter Emegency Full Assistance Program, 1979-1980 (Box 161)
- Legislation: Senate Joint Resolution 23., 1975 (Box 161)
- Photographs: The Farm Group and President Nixon, 1974 (Box 161)
- Departmental: Dept. of Agriculture thru Civil Service Commmision - General Information, 1969-1970 (Box 162)
- Invitations accepted (July 1975 thru December 1976), 1975-1976 (Box 163)
- Invitations: Pending matters; non-urgent; school visits, 1975-1976 (Box 163)
- Leadership thru Foreign Trade, 1979-1980 (Box 164)
- Legislation: Interstate and Foreign Commerse thru Slect Committee on Committees, 1974 (Box 165)
- Departmental: Selective Service thru White House, 1973 (Box 166)
- Departmental: Housing and Urban Development (HUD) thru Office of Economic Opportunity, 1971-1972 (Box 167)
- Departmental: Agriculture thru Employment, Federal, 1974 (Box 168)
- Correspondence, Constituents: Criminal Code thru Taxpayer protection Act, 1982 (Box 169)
- Departmental: Agriculture thru Federal Trade Commission, 1975-1976 (Box 170)
- Lists, Letters, Etc., 1967 (Box 171)
- Congressional Record: Inserts and Statements, 1967-1968 (Box 171)
- Departmental: Agriculture thru Tax Credit on Interest, 1974-1975 (Box 171)
- Past Election Results thru Virginia Voting Statistics, 1953-1965 (Box 171)
- Newspapers: Southwest Virginia Election Results to Grayson County Dams, 1967 (Box 171)
- Legislation: H.R. 4416 Agricutlural Pest Emergancy thru H.J.R. "Jack Jouett" Day, 1981-1982 (Box 172)
- Correspondence, Agriculture Issues: Cotton Inc thru Farm Program Parity, 1979-1980 (Box 173)
- Departmental: Post Office thru Veterans Administration, 1967 (Box 174)
- Departmental: Post Office Department thru White House, 1971 (Box 175)
- Departmental: Administration and Finance, Dept. of thru Virginia, State of, 1982 (Box 176)
- Assorted files, mainly re: state and national deparment requests, 1981 (Box 177)
- Federal Cases A thru Z; Margaret's Cases A thru Z; State Cases A thru Z, 1981-1984 (Box 178)
- Correspondence: T thru XYZ, 1973-1974 (Box 179)
- Departmental: Agriculture thru Defense Supply Agency, 1971-1972 (Box 180)
- Correspondence, Constituents: Virginia Office on Aging thru Norfolk & Western (mostly Virginia departments), 1977-1978 (Box 181)
- Legislation: Burley Tobacco thru H.R. 1325 Repeal Davis/Bacon, 1982 (Box 182)
- Legislation: Aging, Select Committee thru Foreign Affairs, 1976 (Box 183)
- Special Projects and Virginia Tech, 1976-1982 (Box 184)
- Photographs: Posed photos with school groups, families, events, 1973-1975 (Box 185)
- Correspondence: Aging thru K, 1975-1978 (Box 186)
- Title V thru VIDREC, 1982 (Box 187)
- Public Relations: Auctions thru Virginia Farm Bureau Federation, 1979-1980 (Box 188)
- Correspondence, Constituents: Legislation Requests thru Virginia Employment Commission, 1972-1978 (Box 189)
- Correspondence, 96th Congress, Agriculture: Gasahol thru Meat Imports, 1979-1980 (Box 190)
- Correspondence, Constituents: Public Welfare thru Veterans - Facilities, 1981-1982 (Box 191)
- Correspondence, Agriculture Issues: Farmers Home Administration thru GAO Reports, 1979-1980 (Box 192)
- Photographs: William C. Wampler thru Virginia Associaiation of Electric Cooperatives 1979 Nationa Rural Electric Coopertive Associtations Washington Youth Tour, 1979-1980 (Box 193)
- Departmental: Action Agency thru Agriculture Reap Letters, 1973 (Box 194)
- Office Files: Administration thru Sugar, 1982 (Box 195)
- Legislation: Agriculture - Miscellaneous Requests thru Armed Forces - Unionization of Military, 1977-1978 (Box 196)
- Correspondence, Constituents: Photographs thru Wright, David L. (assistant), 1979-1980 (Box 197)
- Pulaski District Office thru Mr. Wampler's Personal Files, 1978 (Box 198)
- Departmental: Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO) Lee County Poverty Program thru Veterans Administration, 1968 (Box 199)
- Invitations declined/closed, 1980 (Box 200)
- Special Projects: Blue Ridge Project No. 2317 thru Projects, General, 1967-1977 (Box 201)
- Correspondence: Virginia Department of Welfare thru Misc. "XYZ", 1966-1967 (Box 202)
- Correspondence: "A" thrue Christmas Letter 1970, 1970 (Box 203)
- Misc "M" to Welfare - Closed, 1981-1982 (Box 204)
- Accounts, 1977 (Box 205)
- Personal invitations and schedules, 1981 (Box 206)
- Correspondence, Constituents: Standards Offical Conduct thru Joint Congeress Operations, 1977-1978 (Box 207)
- Correspondence, Constituents: Abortion thru Economy, 1981-1982 (Box 208)
- Correspondence: Mc thru V, 1974-1975 (Box 209)
- Legislation: Interstate and Foreign Commerse Committee thru Public Works Committee - Highway Program, 1967-1968 (Box 210)
- Departmental: Dept. of H.E.W., Office of Education thru Dept. Of labor, 1969 (Box 211)
- Invitations, 1977 (Box 212)
- Schedules: Appointment Book, 1977 (Box 212)
- Public Relations: 1982 Acceptance Speech thru Mullins Releases, 1978-1983 (Box 213)
- Projects: Bland County Bland-Wythe Water & Sewer Authority thru Bluefield Television (Tazewell), 1967-1972 (Box 214)
- Legislation: H.R. 7233 IMF Authorization thru S.Con.Res. 119 Second Budget FY 81, 1980 (Box 215)
- Correspondence, Constituents: Black Lung thru Fish and Wildlife, 1981-1983 (Box 216)
- Legislation: Postal Changes H.R. 2679 thru Swine Health H.R. 6593, 1979-1980 (Box 217)
- Correspondence: Misc. "A" thru Invitations Accepted July-December, 1967 (Box 218)
- Legislation: Suspensions Week of Sept. 29,1980 thru Railroad Deregulation, 1980 (Box 219)
- Legislation: Joint Economic Committee thru Alien Agriculture Land Ownership, 1977-1978 (Box 220)
- Correspondence: Virginia thru William C. Wampler Personal, 1972-1973 (Box 221)
- Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1971-1972 (Box 222)
- Departmental: Commerce thru Post Office, 1966-1967 (Box 223)
- Departmental: Justice thru White House, 1978 (Box 224)
- Invitations: Closed, 1979 (Box 225)
- Correspondence: Southern Railway thru Virginia Department of Conservation and Economic Develop, 1968-1970 (Box 226)
- Departmental: Army Corps of Engineers thru EPA, 1979 (Box 227)
- Legislation: Committee on Education and Labor - Mine Safety thru Committee on Post Office and Civil Service - Sex-Oriented Material, 1969-1970 (Box 228)
- Departmental: Post Office Department thru Transportation, General Information, 1969-1970 (Box 229)
- Card files: Constituents, S thru Z, regarding Closed Files, 1978-1990 (Box 230)
- Newspapers: The Bristol Herald, 1974-1975 (Box 231)
- Legislation: Surface Mining (publications and information), 1977 (Box 232)
- Correspondence: Agency on Aging thru ROOPTOP of Virginia CAP, 1972-1980 (Box 233)
- Correspondence: Nominations and Committees, 1978-1980 (Box 234)
- Legislation, Virginia: Division of Motor Vehicles thru Miscellaneous, Closed, T-Z, 1979-1982 (Box 235)
- Departmental: Agriculture thru Civil Service Commission (U.S.) 1967 (Box 236)
- Correspondence, 96th Congress: Agriculture Issues: AAM Strikers thru Cotton 1979-1980 (Box 237)
- Legislation: General thru Small Business, 1976 (Box 238)
- Departmental: Agriculture, Dept. of, Imports of Nonfat Dry Milk thru HEW, National Institute of Health, 1973 (Box 239)
- Legislation: Post Office and Civil Service thru Ways and Means, 1975 (Box 240)
- Departmental: Agriculture thru Army, 1967-1968 (Box 241)
- Legislation: Farm Bills: H.R. 4296 Vetoed thru H.R. 7171, Digest and Analysis of Farm Bill, 1975-1978 (Box 242)
- Departmental: Federal Trade Commission thru Interior, Dept. of, U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service, 1979 (Box 243)
- Correspondence, Constituents: Legal Services Department thru Transportation, Dept. of, FAA, 1982 (Box 244)
- Legislation: 16130 Common Situs thru 20000 Interstate and Foreign Commerce, 1977 (Box 245)
- Correspondence: F thru Invitations Accepted April 1969, 1969-1970 (Box 246)
- Campaign: Mailing lists; election returns; press releases, publicity, public relations, including speeches, columns, and audio reels; funding and support information, 1971-1974 (Box 247)
- Correspondence: Congratulatory letters - Campaign thru Pending United Mine Workers of America, 1972-1974 (Box 248)
- Departmental: Academies: U.S. Air Force Academy, U.S. Merchant Marive Academy, U.S. Military Academy, U.S. Naval Academy, 1972-1974 (Box 248)
- Departmental: Housing and Urban Development thru U.S. Postal Service (Oct- Dec 1973), 1973 (Box 249)
- Legislation: Agriculture Committee thru Post Office and Civil Service (Box 250)